http://foundry-eqpt.com/pages/privacy

PrivacyWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co.takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy covers World Equipment and Machine Sales Co's treatment of personally identifiable information that it collects when you are on the World Equipment and Machine Sales Co site.This Privacy Policy covers World Equipment and Machine Sales Co's treatment of personally identifiable information that it collects when you are on the World Equipment and Machine Sales Co site.Information Collection and UseWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co collects personally identifiable information from individuals who provide it voluntarily and knowingly by signing up for mailing lists, filling out forms, etc... This information is used to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials, news, and new products.World Equipment and Machine Sales Co also automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser including your IP address, World Equipment and Machine Sales Co cookie information and the page you requested. We combine this information with similar information collected about all other visitors. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors.Information Sharing and DisclosureWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.World Equipment and Machine Sales Co may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:We have your consent to share the information;We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of World Equipment and Machine Sales Co to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.)We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; orWe believe in good faith that it is necessary to prevent a crime or an injury to ourselves or third partiesCookiesWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co may set and access World Equipment and Machine Sales Co cookies on your computer.Your Ability to delete your entry from the mailing listWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co gives you the ability to delete your entry from its mailing list at any time on its web site.SecurityIn certain areas World Equipment and Machine Sales Co uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWorld Equipment and Machine Sales Co may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pagesMachineryHost website by Machinio
